welcome to category 5 technology TV
欢迎来到5类科技电视
episode number 402 for Tuesday the
星期二的第402集
second of jun 2015 welcome to the show
2015年6月第二届欢迎来到展会
and tonight we are going to indulge our
今晚我们会放纵我们的
need to code our needs a code we are
需要将我们的需求编码为我们的代码
going to start learning how to do PHP
开始学习如何做PHP
functions with our eight segments in the
与我们的八个部分的功能
series beginner to intermediate PHP
系列初学者到中级PHP
stick around all right I should do the
我应该继续坚持下去
news oh yes here's what's coming up in
新闻哦，是的，这里是什么来了
the category five TV news room one
五类电视新闻一类
person's junk is indeed someone else's
人的垃圾确实是别人的垃圾
treasure one of the first 200 Macintosh
珍惜第一台200 Macintosh电脑中的一台
computers ever manufactured was
曾经制造的电脑是
unwittingly donated to a recycling
不知不觉地捐赠给了回收
center who later turned around and sold
后来转身出售
it for nearly a quarter of a million
它接近25万
dollars Facebook is to expand its
美元Facebook正在扩大其
artificial intelligence research opening
人工智能研究开幕
its first lab outside the US in Paris
它在巴黎的美国之外的第一个实验室
Danish toy company Lego has launched a
丹麦玩具公司Lego已经推出了一款
rival to popular video game Minecraft
与流行的视频游戏Minecraft相媲美
max older than a year are vulnerable to
超过一年的最大容易受到影响
exploits that remotely overwrite the
利用远程覆盖的漏洞
firmware that boots up the machine a
启动机器的固件a
feat that it allows attackers to control
它让攻击者可以控制它
vulnerable devices from the very first
首先是易受攻击的设备
instruction stick around the full
指示棒附近
details are coming up later in the show
细节稍后会在节目中出现
this is category 5 technology TV
这是第5类技术电视
starring
主演
Sasha dramatis Hillary Rumble
萨沙dramatis希拉里隆隆
christo wells
克里斯托井
and kid
和孩子
and your host Ravi Ferguson
和你的主人拉维弗格森
you
您
this is category 5 technology TV hey I'm
这是类别5技术电视嗨，我是
Ravi Ferguson I am Sasha dradis welcome
拉维弗格森我是Sasha dradis欢迎
to the show hey category 5 technology TV
到节目嘿类5技术电视
is a member of the tech podcast network
是科技播客网络的成员
if it's tech it's here cat5 TV / tpn and
如果它的技术是在这里cat5 TV / tpn和
also the international association of
也是国际性的协会
internet broadcasters cat five dot TV /
互联网广播公司猫五点电视/
IA ib you have thats how it's done crazy
IA ib你有这样的疯狂
I have to definitely get that done how
我必须明确如何做到这一点
did I ever memorized that cuz you wrote
我曾记住过你写过的那篇文章吗？
it oh yes uh if you have a question that
哦，是的，如果你有问题的话
we might be able to answer give us a
我们可能会 回答给我们一个
call on the cat phone 2545 cat5 TV
呼叫猫电话2545 cat5电视
nobody's calling us we'll call you
没有人叫我们，我们会打电话给你
asacol make it ring Oh give us a call
asacol让它响起哦给我们打电话
today live that would be awesome why not
今天生活，这将是很棒的，为什么不呢
all right um JP JP 0 JP oh maybe on
好的，JP JP 0 JP 哦，也许吧
Twitter got his hands on a new roku and
Twitter得到了一个新的roku和
is watching from his TV which is nice
正在看他的电视，这很好
awesome I want to Roku and you might
真棒我想要Roku，你可能会
also want to Roku which you can buy from
也想要Roku，你可以从中购买
cat five dot TV / Roku it's felt are
它感觉到的猫五点电视/ Roku是
okay you check out and JP nice to be on
好吧，你退房和JP很高兴
your big screen TV yeah our address has
你的大屏幕电视是我们的地址
changed oh yeah you can this is
改变哦，你可以这是
important this is important this is
重要的是，这很重要
important especially if you want to
尤其是如果你想要的话
stamp postcards or premium vinyls
邮票明信片或高级乙烯基
category five stickers oh come on do
五级贴拜托 做
that the first five people to send us
那前五个人发给我们
the stamp postcard will get premium
邮票明信片将获得溢价
vinyl stickers oh we give them a Nepali
乙烯贴纸哦，我们给他们一个尼泊尔人
well giving you an autographed business
给你一个亲笔签名的生意
card as well well what we're gonna do
卡以及我们要做的
now you're going to get the vinyl
现在你会得到乙烯基
sticker if you send us a postcard that
如果你寄给我们一张明信片，贴纸
is stamped so don't put it in an
是盖章的所以不要把它 放在一个
envelope actually stamp it send it to us
信封实际上是邮票发送给我们
and the first five people are going to
前五个人将会去
get the vinyl sticker and everybody who
得到乙烯基贴纸和每个人
sends one and that it arrives before
发送一个，它之前到达
july we're going to put you in a draw
七月我们会把你放在平局中
we're going to be giving away a full set
我们将会放弃 一整套
of the autographed business cards as
作为亲笔签名的名片
well
好
loads of ways to win are so our mailing
我们的邮寄方式非常多
address has changed of course the new
地址已经改变，当然是新的
mailing address is on our website
邮寄地址在我们的网站上
category five dot TV so make sure you
五类点电视，请确保你
get that send us a postcard send us a
得到那寄给我们一张明信片寄给我们一张
Hello whatever you want to do and and
你好，无论你想做什么和
you will have a chance to win some stuff
你将有机会 赢得 一些东西
can I stamp my stamp on the thing as
我可以在邮票上盖上邮票吗？
well you tell us about the stamp you've
那么你告诉我们你的邮票
got the stamping I didn't bring the
得到了我没有带来的冲印
stamp i forgot it at work i've been
邮票我忘了工作我一直
using it at work you've been using it
在工作中使用它，你一直在使用它
are you loving it yeah what's great is
你是否爱 它是伟大的
we ran out of pens we do a lot of
我们用尽了很多笔
drawers well wasn't that convenient see
抽屉也没有那么方便看
all our pens and I the only one who
我们所有的 笔和我唯一的人
could sign stuff yeah exactly so secret
可以签署的东西是完全如此秘密
shopper came in this week I pass you
购物者在本周来到我身边
feel I passed that part if you're
如果你愿意，我觉得我通过了那部分
wondering what on earth we're talking
想知道我们在说什么
about check out episode number 3 99
关于检查第3 99集
where Sasha actually created a stamping
萨沙实际上创造了一个冲压
pen I wish she had brought it with you
笔，我希望她带着它来
please bring him actually show people so
请带他到现场演出
it worked out it's perfect does it look
它发现它看起来很完美
like you actually signed it totally
就像你实际上完全签了字
until I nice I did handling same people
直到我很高兴我处理了同样的人
the same like stamped receipt like same
像同样的盖章收据一样
table as they mated notice exactly and
表，因为他们交配准确和
as I was walking by they were like I'm
当我走过时他们就像我一样
sure this is a stamp I could hear them
当然，这是 我能听到的邮票
grumbling under their voices I saw this
在 他们的声音 下抱怨， 我看到了这一点
on category 5 technology th this is a
在第5类技术上， 这 是一个
stamp she's lazy Shane Milton from
戳她从懒惰巴蒂尔米尔顿
YouTube why you draw your attention to
YouTube为何引起您的注意
another great tool from Linux to find
从Linux找到另一个伟大的工具
out what's eating your hard drive birds
出什么吃你的硬盘鸟
oh yeah so like last week's with a with
哦，是的，就像上周的一个一样
the yeah we're looking at space sniffer
是的，我们正在寻找空间嗅探器
thingy so what changes one is called GD
thingy所以改变一个叫做GD
map and it's available in your favorite
地图，它可以在你最喜欢的
package manager thanks for the tip Shane
包经理感谢Shane提示
awesome possum and duty I like this I
真棒负鼠和责任我喜欢这个我
can just sit and drink my coffee I know
可以坐下来喝我认识的咖啡
good planning Robbie yeah Sasha does all
良好的规划罗比是萨沙做的一切
the talking perfect c 1 28 d called you
说话完美的c 1 28 d给你打电话
out no what did I mom well there was an
没有什么我妈妈好，有一个
error last week the computer that was
上周发生的错误是那台电脑
having trouble with the card reader was
读卡器有问题了
a laptop oh right so I recommended
一台笔记本电脑哦，所以我建议
unplugging the USB from the internal
拔掉内部的USB插头
motherboard isn't possible yeah so with
主板是不可能的，所以
Houdini oh kudi who who'd we know what's
胡迪尼哦库迪谁谁我们知道什么是谁
your name what
你的名字是什么
instead the viewer who sent the question
而不是发送问题的观看者
about the laptop is named yes who do we
关于笔记本电脑被命名为是我们是谁
know maybe yes instead try going to the
知道也许是的，而不是尝试去
BIOS and making note of the settings and
BIOS并记下设置和
then load the optimal default settings
然后加载最佳默认设置
so reset to factory defaults basically
因此基本上重置为出厂默认设置
your BIOS right then reenter the bios
你的BIOS权利，然后 重新进入BIOS
and restore any settings that will not
并恢复任何不会的设置
boot from SD card the SD cards but even
甚至可以从SD卡启动SD卡
that might be remedied if your computer
可能如果您的计算机进行补救
manufacturer offers a BIOS firmware
制造商提供了BIOS固件
update thank you for that message on
更新谢谢你的消息
YouTube c128 d so what what he's saying
YouTube c128 d所以他在说什么
is what you could do is go into the bios
你可以做的就是进入BIOS
reset everything to factory defaults
将所有内容重置为出厂默认值
then you know maybe shutdown might be a
那么你知道也许关机可能是一个
good idea to shut down pull the battery
好主意关闭拉电池
pull the power cord let it power out and
拉动电源线让它断电
then plug everything back in power back
然后把所有的东西都插回去
up go back into the bios set everything
回到BIOS设置一切
back up and that's going to force the
备份和这将迫使
bios to wake up and say oh let's
BIOS 唤醒并说，哦，让我们来
reconnect to that device right good
重新连接到该设备的权利
suggestion thanks for calling me on that
建议感谢给我打电话 对
i didn't even realize obviously i
我甚至都没有意识到 我
thought it was a desktop computer so my
我以为这是一台台式电脑
advice was sound however it did not help
建议是健全的，但它没有帮助
who do we know what so ever it's
我们谁知道这是怎么回事
probably got his laptop apart keyboards
可能是他的 笔记本电脑除了键盘
all broken up to shreds and trying to
所有这些都碎成碎片并尝试着
solder off the USB peripherals from
焊接USB外围设备
motherboard sorry about that so sorry i
主板对不起，我很抱歉
sorry you had two more at the end of the
对不起你有两个在的结束
show is there a disclaimer there is yeah
演出是否有免责声明是啊
you break it you buy it nice first trace
你打破它，你买它很好的第一痕迹
last try school name reflects on last
最后一次尝试学校名称反映在最后
week's news story and share is concerned
本周的新闻报道和分享关注
that servers will generate the heat then
那服务器将会产生热量
that will create or generate quite a bit
这将创造或产生很多
of electricity and who's to pay for it
电力和谁来支付
so oh the heater heater they grab your
所以哦加热器他们 抢 你的
servers so like a wrong a lot of
服务器如此错误很多
electricity in order to run good
电力运行良好
question i think that it would probably
问题我认为它可能会
be offset by the amount you're saving
被您保存的金额抵消
you think it would i guess it depends i
你认为我会猜这取决于我
mean how much does heat cost mystically
意味着神秘的热量花费多少
because if I'm powering a furnace versus
因为如果我为炉子供电而不是
powering a server is it not a balancing
给服务器供电不是一种平衡
scale kind of thing I still like my idea
我仍然喜欢我的想法
best that they should just put them in
最好他们应该把他们放进去
community centers my biggest concern
社区中心我最关心的问题
is not so much about the electricity but
是不是这么多的电力，但
the fact that that the company that's
事实是那家公司
doing the the servers using them as
使用它们的服务器
heaters radiators is they require fiber
加热器散热器是他们需要的纤维
optic internet so you already have to
光纤互联网，所以你已经不得不
have a really strong expensive internet
有一个非常昂贵的互联网
connection wait I think that they are
连接等待我认为他们是
doing that they're laying the lines for
这样做， 他们奠定了行
it do you think they are doing like if
你认为他们是这样做的吗？
they would come into my house and say
他们会来到我家，说
I'll put in the internet I'll pay the
我会在互联网上付钱
hydro you just reap the benefits of this
水电，你只是从中获益
free server there free heat from our
免费服务器有免费的热量从我们的
server yeah that sure sounds too good
服务器是啊，这听起来太好了
they're making money because they're
他们赚钱是因为他们
selling access on their cloud and it's
在云上销售访问权限
got you know docker apps and everything
让你了解码头应用程序和一切
on this cloud that's based on radiators
在这个基于散热器的云上
I live in a basement apartment so I
我住在地下室公寓，所以我
don't know where this is but if you're
不知道这是什么， 但如果你是
in Barry talk to me because I will use
在巴里跟我说话是因为我会用
your feet sounds good um I I should just
你的脚听起来很不错II应该
make mention for you that I did send a
为你提到我确实发了一封
Twitter message a tweet to the company
Twitter消息向公司发送推文
that's making those and I haven't heard
那是在做这些，我还没有听说过
back oh so let you know well certainly
回哦，让你一定知道
let you know if they get back to us on
让你知道他们是否回到 我们身边
that company might be the middle of the
该公司可能是中间 的
night I realized that it's true yeah
晚上我意识到 这是真的是的
seven o'clock Tuesday here what you mean
星期二七点在这里你的意思
they're not watching they're not come on
他们没有注意到他们没有来
and that of course is due to do nurdle
那当然是因为做了一些努力
eyes so tweet them nerda lies with the
他们的眼睛如此鸣叫他们nerda谎言与
zen right um thank you so much to
禅正确的嗯非常感谢 你
anybody who donated it or used our
任何捐赠或使用我们的人
affiliate links and partner links this
联盟链接和合作伙伴链接
week we have pressing needs and your
一周我们有迫切的需求和你的
donations definitely help affiliate
捐款绝对有助于会员
links are a great way to support the
链接是一个很好的方式来支持
show because you can shop on amazon you
因为你可以在亚马逊上购物
can shop on ebay you can shop at B&amp;H
可以在ebay上购物，您可以在B＆H购物
photo-video pretty much anything that
照片视频几乎任何东西
you want these days can be bought on
你想这几天可以买到
amazon it's unreal and they've really
亚马逊这是不真实的，他们真的
done a good job of creating a service i
完成创建一个服务， 我 的一个好工作
ordered something on sunday and it was
星期天点了点东西就是了
here yesterday overnight I and I didn't
昨天在这里过夜，我和我都没有
even pay for shipping I heard on the
即使支付运费就听见
radio that they're starting to do at
他们正在开始 做的 广播
Amazon will do same day shipping if your
亚马逊将做同一天航运，如果你的
amount is over thirty-five dollars
金额超过三十五美元
really same day shipping Elfie as long
真正当天发货的Elfie一样长
as you pay 35 yeah I can't believe that
你交35是的，我不能相信
I get stuff as quickly as I do unless
除非我尽可能快地获得东西
there are situations like I mentioned
有像我提到的情况
that we ordered a case for the Raspberry
我们为树莓订购了一个案子
Pi I did order it from amazon but it was
我从亚马逊订购了它，但它是
a third party seller right and it's
第三方卖家的权利，这是
coming from China it's on a boat
来自中国，它在船上
somewhere and it's taking its sweet time
某处，它正在度过它的甜蜜时光
to get here but anything that I've
来到这里，但我的任何东西
ordered that is sold by amazon gets here
命令由亚马逊销售到这里
right away so you can actually go to our
马上让你真的可以去我们的
website category 5 TV click on support
网站类别5电视点击支持
us and then affiliate links and you'll
我们然后加盟链接，你会
see Amazon and a bunch of other shops
看亚马逊和其他一些商店
there that you can shop with all you
那里你可以和你一起购物
have to do is every time you're going to
必须做的是每次你要去
shop at amazon anyways or any of these
反正亚马逊店或任何这些
shops you click our link and it takes
商店你点击我们的链接，它需要
you to amazon right whatever it is
你不管它是什么，都是亚马逊
exactly and then it just I've done it
正好，然后它就是我做到 了
before it I have done it before it's
在它之前我已经完成了它
easy you cannot mess it up it's better
很容易，你不能搞砸它更好
gauge yeah so anytime we want to know
衡量是的，所以任何时候我们 想知道
how easy something is we just email it
事情是多么容易，我们只是通过电子邮件发送
to Sasha like sorry can you figure this
对萨莎来说，对不起，你能想出这个
out and if she's if she doesn't email
如果她是如果她不通过电子邮件
you back in five minutes then you know
你在五分钟内回来，然后你知道
it's not any good I'm still trying to
这还不是我仍然 想要的
figure out your email that's the problem
找出你的 电子邮件是这个 问题
that's the problem she hasn't figured
这是她没有想到的问题
out email um mike n on youtube was
在youtube上发送电子邮件或者是mike n
watching the backyard BBQ bash episode
看后院烧烤情节
four hundred and commented that it
四百，并评论说
reminded him of some barbecues he hadn't
提醒他一些他没有的烧烤
Barry that had you know less food more
巴里，你知道更少的食物
beer but still that means he's in barrie
啤酒，但仍然意味着他在巴里
which we know you're watching live here
我们知道你在这里住着
in studio like my mom and my sister are
在我的妈妈和我姐姐的工作室里
today hello it's my mom's birthday happy
今天你好，这是我妈妈的生日快乐
birthday happy birthday she's 29 Barry
生日快乐她是29岁的巴里
has changed so much over the years and
多年来发生了很大的变化
our yard is we have the beautiful forest
我们的院子是我们有美丽的森林
and the trees and and it's glorious and
树和它是光荣的
then it's rare to you know it's becoming
那么你很难知道它正在成长
more and more rare to find that in the
越来越难得在中发现
city and it's it's a really great city
城市，这是一个非常棒的城市
but it has changed a lot glad to help
但它变得很乐意帮助
you reminisce exactly come out to the
你的回忆完全出来了
next wouldn't it really works so well if
接下来如果它真的没那么好
we had a whole bunch of beer though no
我们有一大堆啤酒，尽管没有
might have been easier for me you all
对你我来说可能会更容易
noticed how awkward it was for me to
注意到它对我来说有多尴尬
stand shorter than everybody else while
站立比其他人短
it was interviewing them you were on a
它正在采访他们， 你在一个
hill at the bottom I was at the bottom
在底部的山我在底部
of a hell yeah we understand that set me
地狱耶我们明白，定了我
up for failure what are we doing today
失败的故事今天我们在做什么
today we're learning how to create PHP
今天我们正在学习如何创建PHP
functions and I want to take you through
功能，我想带你通过
it we're going to learn
我们将学习
specifically how to save ourselves some
特别是如何自救一些
time save us some redundant coding right
时间节省了我们一些冗余的编码权
are we ready for it is that what you're
我们准备好了吗？ 那就是你
you're getting I yeah I'm well then are
你越来越我是啊我很好，然后是
you ready at home bring up your text
你准备在家里提出你的文字
editor because this is gonna be a lot of
编辑，因为这将是很多
fun we're not using no GUI I might even
有趣的是，我们甚至没有使用GUI
do this in nano what do you think of
在纳米中做这个你觉得怎么样
that I think that's a great idea that's
我认为这是一个好 主意
what I would do mm-hmm thanks Asha
我会 做什么- 嗯，谢谢阿莎
appreciate your support ok so I'm going
感谢你的支持，所以我要走了
to just bring up I am actually you know
只是提出我其实你是知道的
I'm going to have some fun with this
我将有一些乐趣与此
we're going to do this in the terminal
我们要在终端上这样做
let's see what we can do so I'm going to
让我们看看我们能做些什么，所以我要去
just jump over to my temp folder is a
只是跳到我的临时文件夹是一个
place that I can work and what we're
我可以工作的地方以及我们的工作
going to do now this is I'm going to
现在要做，这是 我要去的
give you a number will be at the bottom
给你一个号码将在最后
of your screen there but that number you
你的屏幕在那里，但你的号码
can go over to this website address cat
可以去这个网站地址猫
five dot TV demo doc appt five dot TV /
五点电视演示文档应用五点电视/
there it is and you can actually get
在那里，你实际上可以得到
this code as well okay so we're going to
这段代码还好，所以我们要去
use the terminal so that we can really
使用终端，以便我们真的可以
have some fun and I want to get that
有一些乐趣，我想 明白
here we go ill prepared you jump you
在这里，我们准备好你准备跳过你
threw me into this I'm going to get it
把我扔进这个我要去得到它
23 0 0 23 that's what we're working on
23 0 0 23这就是我们正在努力
okay so where does this what are we
好的，那么 我们 在哪里呢？
actually doing here i'm gonna i'm going
实际上在这里我要去
to create a file here we're going to
在这里创建一个文件，我们要
call this our index well I may have do I
把我们的索引称为我可能 要做的
have an index no I don't index dot PHP
有索引号我不索引点PHP
there we go so we're creating a new file
我们走了，所以我们正在创建一个新文件
in nano called index PHP how do we open
在纳米称为索引PHP 我们如何打开
and close PHP just like that the thing
并关闭PHP就像这样的事情
that we may be tempted to do when we're
我们现在可能会试着去做
coding PHP with what we're what we're
用PHP编码我们就是我们的
about to do we're wanting to save
我们想要保存
ourselves some time when it comes to
我们自己有一段时间
calculations and taking calculations and
计算和计算和
turning them into Lang language or
把它们变成Lang语言或者
verbiage so if I for example if I say he
如果我说，如果我说他的话
wanted to compare 15 items right I might
我想要比较15个项目
be tempted to in that scenario say okay
试图在那种情况下说 好吧
let's say number of items equals let's
让我们假设项目数量等于让我们
make it a player
让它成为一名球员
number so I might be tempted to say if
数字，所以我可能会试图说如果
number of items is greater than one then
然后项目的数量大于一个
we're going to say echo what did I say
我们要说回应我说了什么
he wanted to compare number of items to
他希望项目数比较
compare number of items item right so I
比较项目的数量项目权利，所以我
might be tempted to do it like that and
可能会试图这样做和
then for the singular because if number
然后为单数，因为如果数字
of items is greater than one we're going
的项目比我们要去的要多
to say he wanted to compare a number of
说他想比较一些
items this is a long way this is how
项目这是一个很长的路，这是如何
we're thinking we kind of think in
我们认为我们有种想法
linear terms and we think in logic
线性术语，我们用逻辑思考
logical terms that this is how right I
逻辑上的条件， 这是多么正确的我
might think to do this so then i would
可能会认为这样做，然后我会
say else because now we know that
别说了，因为现在我们知道了
actually number of items is not greater
实际上项目数量并不多
than one so that means it's one or zero
这意味着它是一个或零
but we're not going to encounter that so
但我们不会遇到这样的情况
we would say echo he wanted to say look
我们会说回声他想说的样子
at number of items or I could just say
在物品的数量或我可以说
one cuz I know it's one and this time we
一个因为我知道这是一个，这次我们
have to say what item item right because
不得不说什么项目的权利，因为
it's singular so programmatically it
它是单一的，所以编程它
makes sense mm-hmm and we would say okay
很有意义 - 嗯，我们会说好的
looking that in a linear methodology or
用线性方法或者
mindset that that works but it's a lot
这种工作思路，但它很多
of redundancy I hate redundancy and when
冗余我讨厌冗余和时间
you're working with different languages
你正在使用不同的语言
say you've got a situation where you've
说你有 这种情况
got English French Spanish and or
有英文法文西班牙文和or
perhaps you're just working with a lot
也许你只是在做很多事情
of text and having to make sure that if
的文本和必须确保如果
I make a change to that I need to also
我改变了我 也 需要的
make sure that I make a change to the
确保我改变 了
singular form of that let's run this
让我们来运行这个单数形式
code see let's run it so that you can
代码请参阅让我们运行它，以便您可以
see what it looks like so if i type PHP
看看它是什么样子，如果我输入PHP
index dot PHP he wanted to compare three
索引点PHP他想比较三个
items oh that's perfect now if I open
项目哦，如果我打开，这是完美的
that file again and I say number of
该文件再次和我说的数量
items is one and save it run it again he
项目是一个，并保存它再次运行它
wanted to look at one item notice the
想看一个项目的通知
difference see
区别见
got singular plural yes okay now this is
得到单数复数是的好现在这是
where PHP gets exciting because now we
因为我们现在PHP变得令人兴奋
can start using a programmatic mindset
可以开始使用编程思维
to solve the redundancy issue of having
解决具有冗余问题
to type things multiple times having to
多次输入事物必须
use the logic of if it's greater than
使用大于的逻辑
three then do this if it's less than if
三，然后做这个，如果它少于如果
it's one do this and we've got that
这是一个这样做，我们已经得到了
redundancy and we're really greatly
冗余，我们真的很棒
simplifying it with this example but I
用这个例子简化它，但我
know that there are ways that this can
知道有这种方式可以
be used to save you so much time but at
被用来为你节省很多时间，但是在
the core of what we're doing tonight
我们 今晚要做的核心
we're really learning about how do PHP
我们真的在学习如何做PHP
functions work at their base how can we
功能在他们的基地工作， 我们如何
create a function that we can then call
创建一个我们可以 调用 的函数
over and over and over again to
一遍又一遍地
basically perform the same operation but
基本上执行相同的操作，但是
not have to redundantly type that over
不必重复输入
and over and over again throughout our
并一次又一次地在我们的整个
code and sometimes code can become quite
代码和有时代码可以变得相当
lengthy and quite large this has to do
冗长且相当大，这必须做
with anything from something that's low
与任何东西都很低
locally running in the command line like
在命令行中本地运行
I'm doing here it could be a website
我在这里做它可能是一个 网站
could be an online cart system and you
可能是一个在线购物车系统和你
want to know hey did they put one item
想知道他们是否放了一件物品
in their cart or two items right right
在他们的购物车或右边的两个项目
well how do we get that verbiage without
那么我们如何在没有的情况下获得这种言辞？
having to be redundant that's what we're
必须是多余的，这就是我们的
gonna do okay so let's open up that file
会好起来的，让我们打开那个文件
again and let's say let's take a
再说，让我们来看看
different approach ok Sasha yes we're
不同的方法好萨莎是的，我们是
going to say create a function and this
要说创建 一个功能和这个
works like this okay function first work
这样的作品 可以正常工作
and will say plural that's what we want
并会说复数这就是我们想要的
to do and it looks like that okay okay
这样做， 它看起来像 还好 还好
so we need to now tell our function what
所以我们现在需要告诉我们的功能是什么
it is that we want it to read the data
我们希望它 读取数据
from so i'm going to say i'm going to
从我这么说我要去
create a string we're going to call it
创建一个我们要称之为的字符串
amount so now if I open that up in turn
如果我依次打开它，那么现在的金额
so see I put braces around that that
所以看到我把括号放在那
those braces say okay now that's my
那些大括号说现在好了，那是我的
function anything that happens in here
功能发生在这里的任何事情
is part of the function if I type echo
是功能的一部分，如果我键入回声
dollar sign amount not an apostrophe
美元符号不是撇号
sorry now outside of that function after
对不起现在之外的功能
its declared I can go echo plural and
其宣布我可以去回声复数和
then what 500 notice that I haven't
那么500通知我没有
entered dollars an amount because what
进入美元的数额，因为什么
I'm actually doing is I'm commanding it
我其实是在指挥它
to run
跑步
function and then here's the amount that
功能，然后是这个数量
I'm giving it and what's it going to do
我给它，它会做什么
it's going to echo it so if I now run
它会回应它，所以如果我现在运行
that program it echoes out 500 you see
那个程序会回应你看到的500个
that at the beginning of my line so
那在我的一行开始时如此
let's make it smart let's instead say
让我们让它变聪明让我们改为说
we're going to start with them out and
我们将从他们开始
then we're going to do something kind of
那么我们会做一些事情
fun here we're going to go singular this
有趣的是，我们要去这里
is where language gets exciting and we
语言变得令人兴奋，我们
can go equals quote quote apostrophe
可以去等于引用撇号
apostrophe what that does is that
撇号是什么做的是，
declares that blank is the default so I
声明空白是默认的，所以 我
don't always have to declare this and
并不总是必须声明这一点
plural let's set a what would be a
复数让我们设定一个会是什么
default for something that's plural item
默认情况下是复数项目
or item s yes right typically plural
或项目是对的，通常是复数
would be an asset in ass english
将是一个屁股英语资产
language yes so that will be our default
语言是，所以这将是我们的默认
we can always override it by sending
我们始终可以通过发送来覆盖它
something in the third place for our
在我们的第三位
function what that means is is I can now
功能是什么意思是我现在可以
go echo plural 500 apostrophe apostrophe
去回声复数500撇号撇号
for Singler is empty comma head or as
因为辛格勒是空的逗号头或者
and it will instead add as right okay
它会相反添加为正确的好
that's going to make sense to you in
这对你来说是有意义的
just a second so with that information
只有那么一点信息
now I can go if notice I'm within my
现在我可以去，如果注意到我在我的
function dollar sign amount is greater
功能美元符号量更大
than 1 do this we turn because we're in
因为我们在这里，所以我们转过来
a function we can actually send
我们实际上可以发送功能
something back to the two outside of the
回到了外面的两个东西
function the code that's running in did
功能在没有运行的代码
you use Pico Pico ya know okay why well
你使用Pico Pico你知道为什么好
what is Pico is that it like nano I'm
Pico是什么，它就像我是纳米
using nano yeah it was like nano okay is
使用纳米是啊，它就像纳米好吗
that a different version of the the
那个不同版本的
program yes all right hey I'm the chat
节目是所有权利嘿我是聊天
room for them to say something something
给他们说点什么的空间
that i could say out loud that sounded
我可以大声说出这句话
really smart it's that that was it all
真的很聪明就是这一切
know that PHP is pre hypertext processor
知道PHP是超级文本处理器
well done also smart okay continue okay
做得好也聪明还行继续 还好
alright so now I'm going to return
好吧，现在我要 回去了
something so what does this mean and now
这是什么意思，现在是什么意思
i can return dollar sign plural because
我可以返回美元符号复数因为
amount is greater than 1 notice amount
金额大于1通知 金额
was passed through on the first variable
通过了第一个变量
so else notice how simple that is
所以别人注意到这是多么简单
there's not a lot of code here return
这里没有很多代码返回
singular okay so now we've got a full
单数好吧，现在我们已经满了
function that if I go a number of items
功能，如果我去了一些项目
let's say equals three okay so now if I
比方说，等于三 好吗所以现在如果我
go echo plural number of items which we
去回声我们的复数个项目
know is three it's going to be it's just
知道是三它会是只是
going to output an S see that ass at the
去输出一个S在那看到那个屁股
beginning it says surabhi mm-hmm so how
开始说它surabhi mm-嗯所以如何
does that work so now I go echo item dot
这样做的工作，所以现在我去回声项目点
plural number of items so now in my
现在在我的许多项目
language it says items see that what I'm
语言它说项目看到我是什么
going to do here i'm also going to add a
要在这里做我也要添加一个
PHP end of line and what that's going to
PHP的行尾以及将要发生的事情
do is make it so that doesn't put it
做是为了不把它
before Robbie that just puts a carriage
在Robbie刚刚装上马车之前
return so now it's items okay so now if
现在返回它的项目 好，所以现在如果
number of items is equal to one of
项目的数量等于其中之一
course when I run it it's item it's not
当我运行它时 ，它不是它的项目
going to run it as it's not going to see
将会运行它，因为它不会看到
it as plural so I've now created a
它作为复数，所以我现在创建了一个
function that fully works with anything
功能完全适用于任何事物
that I send to it if the first item is
如果第一件物品是我发给它的
an amount a number okay so 5 10 so I can
一个数字没关系，所以5 10所以我可以
do things like this I can instead of
做这样的事情我可以代替
number of items equals 1 I can instead
项目数量等于1我可以改为
take an array and I can go my array
采取阵列，我可以去我的阵列
equals hello my array equals hi so I now
等于你好我的数组等于你好，所以我现在
have an array that is valued at two
有一个值为2的数组
there are two things in that array so
该阵列中有两件事情
now I can within that I can go count my
现在我可以在那里数数我的数
array and if I run that we know that
数组，如果我运行，我们知道这一点
there are two so it says items so watch
有两个，所以它说的项目如此看
what happens now if we take that and we
如果我们接受这一点，我们现在会发生什么
put it into the context of our cart so
把它放到 我们购物车的背景中
we say he wanted
我们说他想要
to look at or we're going to use the
看看还是我们要用的
verbiage compare and then how many items
措辞比较，然后有多少项目
let's say count dollar sign my array
让我们说数美元符号我的数组
item and then plural or singular okay he
项目，然后复数或单数没关系他
wanted to compare two items alright so
想 比较两个项目 这么好吗
now if i change my array so it only
现在如果我改变我的数组，所以它只
contains one item and run it he wanted
包含一个项目并运行他想要的
to compare one item notice it's not
比较一个项目通知它不是
there's no s at the end of that so where
在那里没有结束，所以在哪里
this gets exciting now okay well you saw
这现在变得令人兴奋了， 好吧，你看到了
that i created a singular form as well i
我创造了一个奇异的形式以及我
can input something for singular and
可以输入一些单数和一些东西
plural so we can do some interesting
所以我们可以做一些有趣的事情
things here with our function and there
这里有我们的功能和在这里的东西
it is that's all that there is to it
这就是它的全部
that's the entire text for this function
这是该功能的全部文本
that we're going to add to our code and
我们将添加到我们的代码和
use it anywhere we want to now because
在我们想要的任何地方使用它，因为
it only has to be declared once and then
它只需要被声明一次
you can use it a million times so let's
你可以使用它一百万次，所以让我们来
say instead compare well how can you
说， 相反，你怎么能
possibly compare one item you cannot
可能会比较一件你不能的东西
doesn't make a whole lot of sense does
并没有做出很多有意义的事情
it so to say he wanted to compare one
这就是说他想比较一个
item to why right so instead we're going
项目为什么正确，所以 我们要去
to say watch this this is kind of neat
说这看起来很 整洁
plural count my array because that's the
复数计数我的数组，因为这是
how many items are in the array we know
我们知道阵列中有多少物品
it's one right now see the array just
这是一个现在只看阵列
above there and so we're going to assign
在那里，所以我们要分配
what would it be in singular form that's
以单数形式是什么？
our first string here so we would say he
我们的第一个字符串，所以我们会说他
wanted to look at say okay but then the
想看看说好，但后来
plural would be compared close that off
复数将被比较接近那个关闭
if I've got my syntax right
如果我的语法正确
then we need to add a space syntax
那么我们需要添加一个空格语法
syntax is like that I didn't do a typo
语法就像我没有做错字
okay grammar okay programmatically
好的语法好的编程方式
grammar basically he wanted to look at
语法基本上他想看
one item see that so now our function
一个项目现在看到我们的功能
not only works with the numbers but it
不仅工作原理与数字，但它
also works with the verbiage so we don't
也适用于这种语言，所以我们不这样做
have to rewrite redundant multiple
必须重写冗余倍数
copies of this verbiage so now if I take
现在，如果我采取这种措辞的副本
that array and I say okay let's let's
该阵列和我说好吧，让我们来
actually make it a few like that okay
实际上让它像这样好吧
run that again and watch what happens he
再次运行并观察他会发生什么
wanted to compare seven items so it's
想要比较七个项目，所以它
changed not only the number the weather
不仅改变了天气的数量
it's plural the word item but also
它是单词项目的复数，但也是
whether he's comparing or looking at
无论他是在比较还是在看
right all within the same function and
所有这些都在同一个功能之内
so that with those little those few
所以那些少数几个
lines of code that's all there is to it
所有的代码行就是这样
I'm able to do all that one thing that
我能够 做到这一切
we can do to now improve this even
我们现在可以做甚至现在改善
further is we can do something really
更进一步的是我们可以真正做到一些
fun because you know what I don't like
有趣，因为你知道我不喜欢什么
you're like really fun I think it's fun
你觉得很有趣我认为这很有趣
look at the joy on my face unlike a
看看我不喜欢我的脸上的快乐
little boy when it comes to code i love
小男孩，当谈到我爱的代码
it i just love code and it's such simple
它我喜欢代码，它非常简单
stuff but it's so fun to when you figure
东西，但它是如此有趣，当你的身影
this stuff out I don't like this count
这东西我不 喜欢这个数
my array and blah blah blah ok so I'm
我的数组等等等等好了，所以我
going to get rid of that my array well
要好好摆脱我的阵列
of course we're going to have a big
当然我们会有一个很大的
problem there i'm going to show you why
问题在那里我要告诉你为什么
so anywhere within my plural i'm going
所以在我的复数形式中我就要去了
to do that now what I'm doing is I'm
要做到这一点，现在我所做的就是我
actually sending my array to plural well
实际上我的阵列发送到复数
that's not going to work because my
这是不行的，因为我的
array is not what it's not a number
数组并不是数字
right it's an array right so what we
这是一个阵列，所以我们
instead do is we say if is array dollar
相反，我们说如果是阵列美元
sign amount hey if it's an array do
签署数量嘿，如果它是一个数组
something a little bit differently let's
有点不同的东西让我们
do this
做这个
dollar sign count equals count see how
美元符号计数等于计数看怎么样
I've now put that my know it was a mount
现在我已经知道这是一座山
sorry can't talk n tight ok so now
对不起，现在不能谈得很紧
dollar sign count is equal to the count
美元符号计数等于计数
the number of variables in the number of
的变量的数量数
keys in dollar sign amount so now it's a
美元符号的金额现在是一个
number it's converted it to a number
号码将其转换为数字
called count so just change all these
称为计数，所以只需更改所有这些
now just that one I guess and then else
现在只是我想的那个， 然后是其他的
here's the this is hey if it's not an
这是嘿，如果它不是
array we know it's a numbers so let's
我们知道这是一个数字，所以 让我们
say count equals int Val so it's an
说计数等于诠释瓦尔，所以这是一个
integer value dollar sign amount so now
现在整数值美元符号量
we've said if it's an array count how
我们已经说过，如果这是一个数组计数如何
many how many there are and that's going
许多有多少那是 怎么回事
to be our account if it's not an array
成为我们的帐户，如果它不是一个数组
we know that it's a number so we're
我们知道这是一个数字，所以我们是
gonna and we're going to force that by
要和我们要强制 通过
changing it to an integer value so that
将其更改为一个整数值，以便
somebody can't break the code by
有人不能通过破解代码
accidentally injecting something else I
不小心注入了别的东西
feel like maybe both myself and songbird
感觉就像我自己和鸣鸟一样
will probably be watching this show over
可能会观看这个节目
and over again like it repeated like
并再次像它重复一样
three seconds exactly three seconds
三秒正好三秒
segments pause ok wait what did that
分段暂停好了，等一下
mean well that's all there's to it so
这意味着所有这一切都是如此
then well you know what's changed now is
那么你知道现在发生了什么变化
my array looks like that but look at my
我的阵列看起来像那样，但看看我的
calls my call is simply plural my array
打电话给我的电话只不过是我的数组
I'm actually now sending the whole array
我现在正在发送整个阵列
to my function I don't have to count it
我的功能，我不必数它
manually anymore right I don't have to
手动了，我没有必要
create that here I don't have to send a
在这里创建我不必发送一个
number it's now the only time that i'm
这是我现在唯一的一次
still using count in this is when i say
当我说的时候，仍然在用这个数字
the number of items ok my array items
项目的数量确定我的数组项目
because that's outside of my plural
因为那不在我的复数之内
function ok so let's run it ok so
功能确定，让我们运行 好吧
nothing has changed other than the fact
除了事实以外没有任何变化
that we are no longer count we're
我们不再算我们了
sending an array and there we go he
发送一个数组，然后我们去他
wanted to compare seven items and it got
想要比较七个项目，它得到了
it just from that and i sent the array
它只是从那我发送数组
so what I'm going to do I'm going to
所以我要去做什么
post the code that i just created live
发布我刚刚创建的代码
on the show i'm gonna post that for you
在节目中， 我 将发布给你
at demo cat five dot TV / 0 to 3 and
在演示猫五点电视/ 0到3和
that way you can look at this you can
这样你就可以看到这个
use that function if you want
如果你想使用该功能
use it in your your own software use it
在你自己的软件中使用它
in your own websites I do find that kind
在你自己的网站中，我确实找到了那种
of functionality pretty handy but I hope
的功能非常方便，但我希望
that you've been able to follow along
你已经 能够跟随
with that look at the code at that
与 看代码在那
address okay and figure out I think
地址好，并找出我认为
that's a great way to learn is yeah it's
这是一个 很好的学习方式
someone else's code figure out how does
别人的代码弄清楚如何
that work and I hope that the having
这项工作，我希望 有
featured it on the show tonight also
在今晚的节目中也有特色
helps you to get your head around it as
可以帮助你将你的头围绕着它
well I think it really really will help
以及我认为这真的会有所帮助
like there were definite parts of that
就像那里有一些明确的部分一样
that I def like that I felt I could get
我确定我觉得我可以得到
there you go and as we already
你去那里，因为我们已经
established earlier on in the show if
如果在展会上成立
sasha gets it then it's easy you said it
萨沙得到它然后你很容易说出来
I did not say it start in many ways I
我没有说我从很多方面开始
feel like a jerk saying that in many
感觉像一个混蛋，说很多
ways different when it comes to
当涉及到不同的方式时
programming mm-hmm little lesson we're
编程 - 嗯，我们是一点点的教训
learning though oh by the way I'm going
通过我的方式学习
to the news desk she's like hey
到新闻台她就像嗨
everybody oh he's a senator she's gone
每个人哦，他是参议员，她走了
well over to the category 5 TV news room
再到第五类电视新闻室
are you ready no I'm not ready over
你准备好了吗？我还没准备好
there may be some time oh well this is
这可能会有一些时间哦
category 5 technology TV welcome to the
5类科技电视欢迎光临
show visit our website triple w category
显示访问我们的网站三重瓦特类
five dot TV find out all the cool things
五点电视找出所有酷的东西
that we've got going on we've got other
我们已经得到了 事情，我们已经有了其他
shows available for you as well if you
如果你愿意，也可以为你提供
want to add the category 5 TV network
想添加5类电视网络
roku channel to your device go to cap
roku频道到您的设备上限
five dot TV / roku channel and that will
五点电视/ roku频道，这将
allow you to subscribe to all of our
让你订阅我们所有的
programming here at category 5 TV thanks
编程在这里5类电视感谢
for tuning in tonight now off to the
现在在今晚调整关闭的
newsroom here is sasha tomatoes it's
新闻室这里是莎莎西红柿
tuesday june the second 2015 and hear
星期二6月第二个2015年和听到
the stories were covering this week our
这些故事报道了本周我们的故事
recycling firm is trying to track down
回收公司正试图追查
the woman who dropped off an extremely
那个女人极其堕落
rare macintosh one computer worth almost
罕见的麦金托什一台电脑值得几乎
one quarter of a million dollars
25 万美元
facebook is opening a new lab in Paris
Facebook正在巴黎开设一个新实验室
focused specifically on the development
专注于发展
of artificial intelligence Lego is
乐高的人工智能
finally bringing out a Minecraft
终于推出了Minecraft
competitor a newfound exploit for max
竞争对手一个新发现的最大值
has been discovered that lets an
已被发现，让一个
attacker remotely overwrite the firmware
攻击者远程覆盖固件
that boots your computer these stories
让你的电脑启动这些故事
are coming right up don't go anywhere
都快来了，别去任何地方
if you need website hosting for your
如果你需要为你的网站托管
website for your blog head on over to
网站为您的博客头向上
cap five dot TV / dreamhost use the
cap five dot TV / dreamhost使用了
coupon code cat five TV we've got fully
优惠券代码猫五电视我们已经充分
SSD hosted lamp stack servers that are
SSD托管灯栈服务器
just waiting for you there and for only
只是在那里等你
seventy dollars a year you're going to
一年你要七十美元
actually receive a calm domain name
实际上收到一个冷静的域名
you're going to get that along with
你会得到这一点
unlimited hosting space unlimited
无限的主机空间无限
bandwidth unlimited email addresses and
带宽无限的电邮地址和
the ability to host an unlimited number
承载无限数量的能力
of domains all covered within that
所有涵盖的域名
seventy dollar fee per year so go to cat
每年七十美元的费用， 所以去 猫
five TV / dreamhost and again use the
五台电视机/ dreamhost再次使用
coupon code cat five TV back to the
优惠券代码猫五电视回来了
newsroom here Sasha I'm Sasha to
新闻编辑室Sasha我是Sasha
radisson here the top stories from the
这里的雷森顶级故事来自于
category five TV news room it turns out
第五类电视新闻室结果
that one person's junk is indeed someone
一个人的垃圾确实是一个人
else's treasure a south bay recycling
其他的宝藏南湾回收
firm is looking for a woman who in early
公司正在寻找一名早期的女士
April dropped off boxes of electronics
4月份放弃了电子箱
that she had cleaned out from her house
她已经从她的房子里清理出来了
after her husband died about two weeks
她的丈夫在约两周后死亡
later the firm clean Bay Area discovered
后来公司清理湾区发现
inside one of the boxes a rare find a
在其中一个盒子里有一个罕见的发现
vintage apple one one of only about 200
复古苹果只有200人左右
first-generation desktop computers put
第一代台式电脑放
together by Steve Jobs Steve Wozniak and
一起由史蒂夫·乔布斯史蒂夫·沃兹尼亚克和
Ron Wayne in 1976 the company had a
1976年Ron Wayne公司有一个
backup of donations and didn't
捐款的备份并没有
immediately go through her boxes the
立刻穿过她的箱子
recycling firm sold the apple one this
这家回收公司卖掉了苹果
month for two hundred thousand dollars
月为二十万美元
to a private collection and now because
到 私人收藏，现在因为
the company policy is to split proceeds
公司的政策是分拆收益
5050 with the donor he's looking for the
5050与他正在寻找的捐助者
mystery woman who refused to get a
神秘女人谁拒绝得到一个
receipt or to leave her name oh I know
收据或留下她的名字哦，我知道
to get her $100,000 check the woman just
为了让她10万美元检查女人
needs to show up at the company's
需要出现在公司的
warehouse because the man who accepted
仓库因为接受的人
the donation said to prove who she is
该捐款表示证明她是谁
all he needs to do is look at her that
他所需要做的就是看着她
is really sweet Robbie like it firstly
Robbie首先非常喜欢它
it's sad and secondly it's really sweet
它很伤心， 其次它真的很甜
it's nice to know that they're doing
很高兴知道他们在做什么
their best I mean here we are in Canada
他们最好的我是说 我们 在加拿大
and they're trying so hard to track her
他们正在努力追踪她
down yeah you imagine though dropping
放下你想象中的东西
off what you think is junk and this is
关掉你认为是垃圾的东西，这是
old stuff
老东西
I mean it look it how would you know
我的意思是它看起来如何，你会 知道
that it was not just a bunch of circuit
这不仅仅是 一堆电路
boards and and junky stuff two hundred
董事会和垃圾东西两百
thousand dollars it's sold for well and
一千美元它卖得很好
I mean I'm just trying to empathetically
我的意思是我只是在努力 去换位思考
putting my feelings on to her but i'm
把我的感情放在她身上，但我是
thinking like she her husband just died
像她丈夫刚刚去世一样思考
so she's probably going through all this
所以她可能会经历这一切
stuff and she's full of emotion and
东西，她充满了情感和
she's already heartbroken about having
她已经伤心欲绝了
to get rid of this stuff so once they do
一旦他们这样做就摆脱这种东西
track her down and give her the check
追踪她并给她支票
it'll probably just kind of put a nice
它可能只是一个很好的
sweet lining on you know such a bitter
你知道这样的苦涩衬里
process in that process so hopefully I
在那个过程中，希望我能够过程
find her they give her the money so
找到她，他们给了她这么多钱
Facebook is to expand its artificial
Facebook正在扩大其人造
intelligence research opening its first
情报研究首次开放
lab outside the US in Paris the team
实验室在美国巴黎以外的团队
will work on ambitious long-term
将在雄心勃勃的长期工作
projects including natural language
项目包括自然语言
processing and speech and image
处理和语音和图像
recognition Facebook's chief technology
承认Facebook的主要技术
officer Mike short fur said that the
军官迈克短毛皮说的
threat of a I had been overblown in
一个人的威胁被夸大了
recent months yan look hon who heads up
最近几个月， 看起来很高兴
Facebook's AI research said that we have
Facebook的人工智能研究表示，我们有
nothing to worry about in the near
没有什么可担心的
future he believes it will be several
未来他相信会有几个
decades before we see human level AI and
几十年之后，我们看到了人类的AI和AI
says this gives the AI community and
说这给了AI社区和
industry plenty of time to talk about
行业充足的时间来谈论
the ethics a is one of the three pillars
伦理a是三大支柱之一
of investment for the company the others
对其他公司的投资
being virtual reality and connectivity
虚拟现实和连接性
initially six research scientists will
最初有六位科研人员会
be based in the Paris lab growing to 12
总部设在巴黎实验室，增长到12个
by the end of the year why Paris of all
到今年年底为什么巴黎所有
places like why I don't understand the
像我为什么不理解的地方
Paris because they like their wine their
巴黎，因为他们喜欢自己的酒
ladies and their a I it's it's so good
女士和他们一个我 这是如此的好
well you know what there's a there's a
那么你知道那里有什么
large number of people focused
大量的人关注
specifically on artificial intelligence
特别是关于人工智能
development in Paris so it really is a
在巴黎的发展，所以它真的是一个
good location for facebook to go to but
Facebook的好位置去，但
with the comments about you know well
关于你的评论很清楚
it's were so many years off from
这是多少年了
artificial intelligence you know and and
人工智能你知道和
we're why are we afraid I I think it
我们是为什么我们害怕我认为它
really reminds me of what the
真的让 我 想起 了什么
conversations must have been like you
对话一定是像你一样
know before pollution and you know well
知道污染之前，你知道得很好
oh well we're so many years
哦， 我们好多年了
off its you we don't need to make wise
关掉你我们不需要做出明智的决定
choices yet and it seems a little bit we
选择还没有，我们似乎有点儿了
should probably talk about these silly
应该可能谈论这些愚蠢的
yeah we should talk about the ethics
是的，我们应该谈论道德
before we go ahead and do all of you i
之前，我们继续前进，做所有的 你我
really think you kind of need to plan
真的认为你需要计划
for ethics when you're building
为了道德，当你在建造
something such as you know that's what
一些诸如你知道那是什么
you're working toward okay you're
你正在朝着好的方向努力
obviously you brought it up so you're
显然你把它带来了， 所以你
working toward artificial intelligence
致力于人工智能
that is human-like mm-hmm realistically
那就是逼真的人性化
though I mean it starts with okay
尽管我的意思是它开头的好
they're gonna create advertising systems
他们会创造广告系统
and so I think your advertising system
所以我认为你的广告系统
should probably have a certain level of
应该可能有一定的水平
ethics as well maybe they don't have
伦理也可能是他们没有的
arms and legs and I can't go around
胳膊和腿，我不能走动
beating people up but they should be
打人，但他们应该是
ethical yeah I'd say slippery slope once
道德是的我会说滑坡一次
you start right so this is fun news the
你开始吧，所以这是好消息
image to accompany Lego has launched a
形象陪乐高推出了一款
rival to popular video game Minecraft
与流行的视频游戏Minecraft相媲美
Lego world is available now at a four
乐高世界现在有四个
hour 11 nine or eleven dollars and
小时11 9或11美元
ninety-nine cents not with pounds but I
九十九美分不与磅，但我
don't know how to say that 11 11 pounds
不知道怎么说11 11磅
ninety-nine pen sir via the steam gaming
通过蒸汽游戏的九十九个先生
platform its final release featuring
平台的最终版本特色
classic and modern playsets and popular
经典和现代的玩具和流行
min mini figurines is expected in 2016
预计2016年将推出迷你小雕像
features will be added in response to
功能将被添加回应
feedback from players of the game Lego
来自乐高游戏玩家的反馈
already sells minecraft playset so
已经销售了我的玩具游戏套装
gamers can physically build their
玩家可以在身体上建立自己的
virtual collection or creations and lego
虚拟收藏或创作​​和乐高
worlds will invite fans to do the same
世界将邀请粉丝们也这样做
in reverse Tom stone managing director
反向汤姆石执行董事
of TT games which will release Lego
的TT游戏将释放乐高
world's said it embodies the physical
世界说它体现了物理
Lego brick building fund that consumers
乐高砖建筑基金消费者
have enjoyed for decades on a digital
几十年来一直在数字上享受
platform that now delivers an entirely
现在提供完整的平台
new type of experience with the beloved
与心爱的新型体验
bricks from the brick by brick editor to
从砖头编辑砖块到砖块
discovering an expansive range of items
发现一个广泛的项目
characters and creatures to populate
角色和生物来填充
your world the creative possibilities
你的世界创造性的可能性
are endless he added Daniel Goldberg who
他加入了丹尼尔戈德堡，他是无止境的
has written a book about the growth of
已经写了一本关于增长的书
Minecraft said that he was surprised
Minecraft说他很惊讶
that it had taken this them this long I
它已经把 他们这么长时间 带走 了
agree now that i think about it because
现在同意我认为这是因为
lego and minecraft seem like they're
乐高和我的世界似乎就像他们一样
sort of blocky the same you know what's
有点像块，你知道什么
funny about that statement
有趣的声明
that when people say to me I don't
当人们对我说，我不知道
understand the appeal of Minecraft or in
了解Minecraft或英特尔的吸引力
our case mind test I tend to say it's
我们的情况心智测试我倾向于说
really like a modern-day lego it's your
真的很喜欢 现代的 乐高，这是你的
building you're creating and revenue
建立你的创造和收入
jank is in the chat room and says
jank在聊天室里说
virtual Lego I'd much rather the real
虚拟乐高我宁愿真实
thing and it's true but as a dad of
事情，这是真的，但作为一个爸爸
young kids a lot of space and a lot of
年轻的孩子很多空间和很多
money they're extremely expensive so to
钱他们非常昂贵，所以
be able to we may not understand the
能够我们可能不了解的
currency but 11 pounds ninety-nine pence
货币，但11磅九十九便士
yeah I think its patents panzon so we'll
是的，我认为它的专利Panzon，所以我们会
just wrap oh yeah we'll just well 12
只是包装哦耶 我们会 很好12
pounds about 12 pounds I it's a lot
英镑约12磅我很多
cheaper than going out and getting the
不是走出去 ，让便宜
real thing to be honest with you well
真实的东西来跟你 说实话 好
plus you can't like in the middle of the
再加上你不能的中间像
night when you're getting up to feed the
晚上当你 准备喂食时
baby step on a virtual Lego block oh
宝贝踏上虚拟乐高积木哦
that hurts and there that obviously
那显然会伤害你
there's there's the whole tactile feel
那里有整个触觉
of real Lego but I think there's a
真正的乐高，但我认为有一个
really good place for it and it's about
这是真正的好地方，这是关于
time they did this it just does make
时间他们 这样做只是 确实让
sense yeah they said minecraft is
感觉是的，他们说我的世界是
exactly what Lego should have done ten
正是乐高应该完成的十件事
years ago here here so kind of awesome
几年前在这里这里真棒
max older than a year are vulnerable to
超过一年的最大容易受到影响
exploits that remotely overwrite the
利用远程覆盖的漏洞
firmware that boots up the machine a
启动机器的固件a
feat that allows attackers to control
壮举让攻击者可以控制
vulnerable devices from the very first
首先是易受攻击的设备
instruction the attack effects max
指示攻击效果最大
shipped prior to the middle of 2014 that
在2014年中之前发货
are allowed to go into sleep mode a
被允许进入睡眠模式a
malicious user could reflash a max by us
恶意用户可以通过我们重新刷新max
using functionality contained in user
使用用户中包含的功能
land which is the part of an operating
作为经营的一部分的土地
system where installed applications and
系统安装的应用程序和
drivers are executed by exploiting
驱动程序通过利用来执行
vulnerabilities such as those regularly
像那些定期的漏洞
found in Safari and other web browsers
在Safari和其他网页浏览器中找到
attackers can install malicious firmware
攻击者可以安装恶意固件
that survives hard drive reformatting
在硬盘重新格式化后仍然存在
and reinstallation of the operating
并重新安装操作
system the attack is more serious than
系统的攻击比比较严重
the Thunderstrike proof-of-concept
Thunderstrike证明概念
exploit that came to light last year
去年发现的漏洞
while both exploits give attackers the
而两种攻击都会给攻击者带来攻击
same persistent and low level control of
同样的持久和低水平的控制
a Mac the new attack doesn't require
Mac上新的攻击并不 需要
even brief physical access as the
即使是短暂的身体访问
thunderstrike did
雷暴打击了
means attackers halfway around the world
意味着世界各地的攻击者
may remotely exploit it at the moment
目前可以远程利用它
there isn't much use of vulnerable
没有太多的弱势使用
machine or there isn't much users of
机器还是没有 太多的用户
vulnerable machines can do to prevent
脆弱的机器可以做到预防
exploits other than to change default OS
除了更改默认操作系统以外的漏洞利用
X settings that put machines to sleep
让机器进入休眠状态的X设置
when not in use so if your if your
当不用时如果你的话如果你的
computer never goes to sleep then is
电脑永远不会睡觉，然后是
that if it never goes to sleep it'll
如果它永远不会睡觉它会
never be a problem I guess that's where
从来没有成为一个问题， 我想这是在哪里
the problem lies I is hey during the
问题在于 我是嘿嘿
sleep mode transaction or whatever but
睡眠模式交易或其他任何
that's kind of scary I mean these aren't
这有点吓人我的意思是这些不是
even really that old systems you talk in
即使真的那么老的 系统你谈论
five years and older right so definitely
五岁以上的权利如此明确
the one that we talked about earlier
我们之前谈到的那个
that one's susceptible he hates anything
那个人容易受到伤害，他讨厌任何事情
else that has been released in the past
其他在过去已经发布的
couple of years yeah well and see it
几年来很好，看到它
makes me worried because people i think
让我担心，因为我认为的人
go under this false sense of security
在这种虚假的安全感下
that macs are safer safest safer it's
这是最安全的mac电脑更安全
really letting sense what oh you know
真正让 感觉 什么哦，你知道
where well a mac and linux fall into the
mac和linux在哪里？
same kind of blanket of it's not that
不是那样的毯子
they're impenetrable it's that they are
他们是坚不可摧的
safer than the Microsoft alternative so
比微软的替代品更安全
max are bound to have exploits just like
最大限度必然会有类似的漏洞利用
Linux is but it's going to be a lot less
Linux是但它会少得多
than say windows for example but this is
比如说窗户，但是这是
this is a big one and because there's no
这是一个很大的问题，因为没有
real fix for it at this point I mean
我的意思是在这一点真正解决它
hopefully there will be something that
希望会有一些东西
comes out but we're talking flashing
出来了， 但我们在说闪光
firmwares on every Mac that was sold
每台Mac上出售的固件
before five years ago that's pretty
在五年前这很漂亮
messy I wonder whether or not they'll do
凌乱我不知道他们会不会做
it can they do a recall what they do
它可以回忆他们做什么
like a car recall know what they do a
像汽车召回知道他们做了什么
computer Mac fanboys I just have to
我只需要电脑的Mac fanboys
upgrade that's the rule right is
升级这是正确的规则
obsolete you gotta upgrade yeah oi yeah
过时了，你得升级耶噢耶
well big thanks this week to roy w nash
非常感谢这个星期罗伊w纳什
and our community of viewers for
和我们的观众群体
submitting stories to us if you found a
如果你发现了一个故事，就向我们提交故事
story a news story that you'd like to
故事的新闻故事，你想
send email to newsroom at category 5 TV
发送电子邮件到新闻室5类电视
for all your tech news with a slight
对于你所有的科技新闻都有轻微的影响
linux bias visit the category 5 TV news
Linux偏见访问5类电视新闻
room at newsroom category 5 TV for the
新闻室5类电视机房
category 5 TV news room i'm sascha
第5类电视新闻室我是莎莎
dermis
真皮
thanks Sasha this is category 5
谢谢Sasha，这是第5类
technology TV welcome to the show it's
技术电视欢迎来到它的展会
episode number 402 that means there are
第402集意味着有
four hundred and two hours of this stuff
这些东西有四百零二小时
available for you on our website
在我们的网站上为您提供
category five TV or of course you can
五类电视或当然你可以
also find us on roku find us on YouTube
也可以在roku上找到我们在YouTube上找到我们
finest pretty much anywhere you get your
最好的地方，你得到你的任何地方
programming from we'd love to have you
我们很乐意为您编程
participate in the show and become part
参加展会并成为其中的一员
of our community all right do we have
我们的社区是好的，我们有
some viewer questions leave we could get
一些观众的问题离开我们可以得到
in do you have you requested great
你有没有要求太棒了
they're coming in where hey to our chat
他们会来我们聊天的地方
room is well nice to see everybody I
房间很高兴见到我的每一个人
love the chat room well no I said that I
爱聊天室，我没有说过
know I said that on the four hundredth
我知道我说的是第四百
episode I will say it every episode I
情节我会在每一集我都说
love the chatter we need to say that
爱需要我们说，喋喋不休
that's fine yeah can I say hello to some
这很好，我可以向一些人问好
of our newly registered viewers we've
我们新注册的观众
got vbd 1804 who just recently
刚刚得到vbd 1804
registered on our website category 5 TV
在我们的网站5类电视上注册
sometimes people have been watching for
有时人们 一直在关注
some time and then suddenly decide oh
有些时候，然后突然决定哦
maybe I should register for the website
也许我应该注册该网站
that's a way that you can accumulate
就是这样 ，你 可以积累 方式
things like viewer points and
像观众点和
participate in some of the competitions
参加一些比赛
that we have there to find yourself on
我们在那里找到自己
the homepage of our website there is a
我们网站的主页有一个
new register here called grumpy hamster
这里的新注册称为脾气暴躁的仓鼠
grumpy hamster oh I like it Alasdair and
脾气暴躁的仓鼠哦，我喜欢它阿拉斯代尔和
drais or it's nice to have you
或者很高兴有你
registered on our website as well
也在我们的网站上注册
joining our community in Spain gando me
加入我们在西班牙的社区gando me
a new and alpha omega 777 7 7 7 welcome
一个新的和阿尔法omega 777 7 7 7欢迎
to the show those aren't even seven
到表演那些甚至不是七
sevens I will say that's 67 s right Alf
我会说这就是67秒吧
omega-6 Evans okay now we got figured
欧米茄-6埃文斯现在好了，现在我们想通了
out welcome alright question from Bob
出来鲍勃欢迎好的问题
hey Bob I would like to watch the google
哎鲍勃·我想 观看谷歌
hangout you mentioned on the cat5 show
你在 cat5节目中提到的环聊
but i don't want want to join or use
但我 不想加入或使用
google in any way if i can help it is
谷歌以任何方式，如果我可以帮助 它
there a way to watch without John O'Shea
没有John O'Shea就有办法看
in your face Google machine okay so via
在你的脸上谷歌机器 好，所以通过
Roku not affiliated with with Google in
Roku与Google无关
any way shape or form go to cap 52 TV /
任何形式或形式的方式去盖52电视/
Roku ROK you we've talked about it on
Roku公司韩国你，我们已经 在 谈论 它
the show
演出
already get one of those you'll be able
已经得到了你将能够的其中一个
to find Google Plus hangouts in special
要特别寻找Google Plus环聊
features you'll see all that kind of
功能你会看到所有的那种
stuff there there's backstage videos
那里有后台的视频
there's behind the scenes there's extras
幕后有幕后演员
that have been submitted by co-hosts
已由共同主办方提交
stuff that has nothing to do with the
与此无关的东西
show that's just like home movies and
结果表明，就像家庭电影和
stuff that you can enjoy fun stuff on
东西，你可以享受有趣的东西
our roku channel as well okay so you
我们的roku频道以及好，所以你
don't want to sign up for google but
不想注册 谷歌，但
there are ways to watch that without
有没有方法可以观看
actually signing up go to linux tech
实际上注册去linux技术
show com it looks just like that and
显示com它看起来就像那样和
what that's going to do is it is going
那将会发生什么
to redirect you to our YouTube channel
将您重定向到我们的YouTube频道
Linux text show and that's fine you're
Linux文本显示，这很好
not going to have to sign up for google
不会有报名 参加 谷歌
in order to access this as you know you
以便像您所了解的那样访问这些内容
can use YouTube without having a google
可以在没有谷歌的情况下使用YouTube
account now i'll just say out the gate
现在我要说出门
that we prefer you to have a google
我们希望你有一个 谷歌
account because then you can like our
因为那时你可以喜欢我们的帐户
videos you can share our videos more
视频，你可以分享我们的视频更多
effectively you can give it the thumbs
有效地，你可以给它大拇指
up you can comment those things are all
你可以评论这些东西都是
very important to to us and we like to
对我们来说非常重要，我们喜欢
interact with our viewers as well so
与我们的观众互动也如此
jumping over here what do you see I've
跳过这里你看到我有什么
clicked on playlists and then you see
点击播放列表，然后你就会看到
Google Plus hangout that's the who I
Google Plus视频群聊，这就是我
almost wore that shirt again today oh
今天再次穿上那件衬衫哦
yeah so there you go it's as simple as
是的，所以你去那里就像
that and then you've got the Google+
然后你就有了Google+
Hangout you can you can scroll through
环聊你可以翻阅
that's a full hour behind the scenes
这是幕后的整整一个小时
with the crew here at category 5 TV and
与在5类电视和船员在这里
that includes your live tour of the
包括你的现场直播
studio as well yeah that's a lot of fun
工作室以及耶，这很有趣
see studio D that's how you can do it as
看到工作室 D这就是 你如何做到这一点
well there you go two ways you can watch
那么你有两种方法可以观看
awesome dreamer sorry Dreamweaver 909
令人敬畏的梦想家抱歉Dreamweaver 909
says i love my Roku it's great I don't
说我爱我的Roku这很好，我不知道
need high priced cable I have this
需要高价的电缆我有这个
discussion with garbey earlier today
今天早些时候与Garbey的讨论
says I don't understand the what the
说我不明白那是什么
Roku is really for because I can use my
Roku真的是因为我可以用我的
chromecast and I think for the novice
chromecast和我认为的新手
user especially for my kids for my
特别是为我的孩子用户
family and me included in that to be
家人和我包括在内
able to sit down in front of the TV with
能够坐下 来在电视机前
a Roku where I've got a remote control
我有遥控器的Roku
that's a TV remote control it's not a
这是一个电视遥控器，它不是
smartphone it's not a right it's not a
智能手机它不是一个权利，这不是一个
computer device it's not a keyboard or
电脑设备它不是一个键盘或
anything like that it's a it's a remote
就像它是一个遥控器
control and I'm literally
控制和我字面上
quite literally channel flipping without
毫不夸张地说，频道翻转没有
the need for cable and finding all these
对电缆的需求并找到所有这些
great channels that are available on
伟大的渠道，可用
roku and being able to just go from
roku和能够从中走出
channel to channel and find out what
渠道渠道，并找出什么
programming they've got there we found
编程他们到了那里我们发现
some really great shows on roku and it's
一些非常棒的节目在roku上
on demand in a lot of cases there's live
在很多情况下都需要现场直播
video as well but because it's on demand
视频，但因为它是按需提供的
you can just start a video at the very
你可以在一开始的视频
beginning of the show at any time that
在任何时候开始的节目
you want so so for me it's really about
你想的那么所以对我来说，这的的确确是
being able to sit down in front of the
能够坐在 前面
TV big screen and joy and HD experience
电视大屏幕以及高清和高清体验
that is TV not computer so I don't feel
那是电视而不是电脑，所以我不觉得
like I've got a computer connected to my
就像我有一台连接到我的电脑
TV and I'm bringing up websites and
电视和我正在建立网站和
streaming to my TV right it's not like
流媒体到我的电视权利它不是
that it's like TV but without the
这 就像电视，但没有
expensive cable it's kind of awesome
昂贵的电缆这真是太棒了
it's really awesome really looking
真的很棒
forward to getting one hasn't happened
前进得到一个没有发生
yet very well can you Roku your home
但你很好，你可以在你的家里
videos Reb D Genk asks and there is a an
视频Reb D Genk问，有一个
app that you can installer a channel
应用程序，你可以安装一个频道
that you install on your Roku called
你安装在你的Roku上
plex there are other ones as well and
还有其他的也有
I've experienced many of them but Plex
我经历了许多，但Plex
is the one that I absolutely adore you
是我绝对崇拜你的那个
install on one of your computers you
安装在你的一台电脑上
install the plex media server it can be
安装它可以的Plex媒体服务器
a linux computer can be a windows
一台linux电脑可以成为一个windows
machine it can be a server I've got it
它可以是一台服务器，我已经得到它
installed on my unraid server for
安装在我的unraid服务器上
example as a virtual mission or as a
作为一个虚拟的使命或作为一个例子
plug-in and so then what it does is it
插件等，然后它做了什么
transcodes the video on the fly sends it
随时对视频进行转码发送
to your Roku and it works just like a
到你的Roku，它就像一个
channel to so all my home movies we can
通道，以便我们所有的家庭电影
flip through and watch them on our roku
翻转过来，在我们的火车上观看它们
and as many Roku's as we have in the
和我们在这里一样多的Roku
house so yes you can it just requires
房子所以是的，你可以只是需要
that extra thing be installed well
多余的东西安装好
that's not a problem is it oh nice okay
这不是一个问题，它哦，很好，没关系
I have a question from voodoo Sandman
我有一个来自伏都教桑德曼的问题
it's actually not a question it's a
这实际上不是一个问题
comment in Panama coding tool so he
巴拿马编码工具评论，所以他
wants you to check out this great coding
希望你看看这个伟大的编码
tools yes arduino a coding tools yeah
工具是arduino一个编码工具是的
arduino so if you could share that link
arduino所以如果你可以分享该链接
let me pull it up here super I'm just
让我把它拉到这里超级，我只是
bringing up the email cuz I didn't
提起电子邮件因为我没有
actually have those dark I like to do
实际上有我喜欢做的那些黑暗
that oh by the way yes um that Pico
顺便说一句，哦，那个 Pico
thing that's not nano that's a coding
这不是纳米，这是一个编码
thing from before nano from a long way
从纳米之前的事情，从很长的路要走
back in the day way back playback
在当天返回回放
when I had hair that's right and I knew
当我有头发是正确的，我知道
that yeah this comes to us from voodoo
这是从巫术来到我们这里
Sandman it's the alternative arduino
桑德曼是替代arduino
interfaces software i will post the link
接口软件我会发布链接
for you in the chat room as well as on
为你在聊天室以及
our website category 5 TV category five
我们的网站类别5电视类别 五
dot TV and business will be on the show
网络电视和商业将在节目中亮相
notes page 4 episode number 402 are do
第4集第402集是做的
block a programming environment designed
阻止设计的编程环境
to make physical computing with Arduino
使用Arduino进行物理计算
as easy as drag and drop instead of
就像拖放而不是拖放一样简单
writing code worrying about your syntax
编写担心你的语法的代码
and miss placing semicolons our do block
并错过放置分号我们的阻止
allows you to visually program with a
允许你用一个可视化的程序
snap together list of code blocks that's
将代码块列表拼接在一起
pretty cool so it gives you a way to
很酷，所以它给你一个方法
code your Arduino without actually
无需实际编码您的Arduino
having to do a whole bunch of code kind
不得不做一大堆 代码
of reminds me that interface really
提醒我 那个界面真的
looks a lot like unreal for for me okay
看起来很像虚幻为我好吗
I think that that is how I think oh yeah
我认为这就是我的想法哦
yes so what's the green one well that's
是的，那么绿色的是什么？
probably those little cool any things
可能这些小东西很酷
that you put on all right yeah okay got
你穿上没事就好了
it mr. Chris Chris Lee hey Chris Chris
它先生。 克里斯克里斯 李嘿克里斯克里斯
Lee 2511 okay I live in the UK I can
李2511 好吧我住在英国我可以
tell the difference between the sky and
告诉天空和天空之间的差异
skype logos do you know that oh boy that
你知道，Skype的标志哦，那个男孩
was like six weeks ago in the news so
就像六周前 在新闻等等
you live there and you can tell the
你住在那里，你可以告诉
difference oh you're in the minority my
区别哦，你在少数我的
friend apparently yes because the
朋友显然是因为
government or the the court system
政府或法院系统
doesn't really understand he does
他真的不明白他的意思
understand that the word skype does have
明白Skype这个词有
the word sky in it hmm but he can see
天空中的词嗯，但他可以看到
you know the difference between the
你知道的区别
color scheme and the cloud around skype
配色方案和围绕Skype的云
that's just the way this so thank you
这只是 方式会这样谢谢
for supporting us Oh c128 d who we heard
为了支持我们哦c128 d我们听到了谁
oh yes commenting on YouTube now sending
哦，是评论YouTube 现在发送
us e-mail as well thanks for
我们的电子邮件，以及感谢
participating on the show okay so sorry
参加该节目好吧，真抱歉
that I couldn't be on the live stream
我不能在现场直播
last night I had a meeting to do the
昨晚我有一个会议去做
reason why is it not X with a yes
为什么它不是一个是的
knoppix says that it's a problem with KD
knoppix说这是KD的问题
and lies this must be referring to that
谎言这一定是指那个
question where he was having trouble
问他在哪里遇到麻烦
with the interface yeah
与 界面是啊
the menu system yes is that the
菜单系统是的
installer creates the incorrect syntax
安装程序创建不正确的语法
in the start menu and that they should
在开始菜单中，他们应该
fix the Installer instead of knoppix
修复安装程序而不是knoppix
fixing it on their end okay so when you
把它固定在它们的末端好，所以当你
install kdenlive it grates bad links the
安装kdenlive它感觉糟糕的链接了
other distros did not suffer from the
其他发行没有遭受
same problem wonder what causes it then
同样的问题想知道是什么导致它
I would love now we only have about
我想现在我们只有约
eight minutes left the show and so maybe
八分钟离开了节目，所以也许
we could set this one aside I know if
我们可以把这一个放在一边，我知道如果
you want to leave it unchecked recycling
你想让它不受检查的回收
weekend so if we come back to this
所以如果我们回到这个周末
question next week and you think you've
下周的问题，你认为你已经
heard it before I'm hoping that we will
在我希望我们会的之前听到它
come back to that for you see 128 d
回到那个你看到128 d
because perhaps we would have time to
因为也许我们有时间
bring up knoppix I'll I'll see what
提出knoppix我会看到什么
happens when we install Kate and live
当我们安装Kate并且生活时发生
and then see what what it does you can
然后看看它能做什么
see if we can help you with that but i
看看我们能否帮助你， 但我
think my original suggestion was maybe
想想我的原始建议也许
try creating your own links that's
尝试创建自己的链接
there's no problem doing that throw them
这样做并没有问题
on your desktop whatever you want to do
在你的桌面上，无论你 想做 什么
um Michael hey Mike um went to balnaird
迈克尔，迈克，他去了balnaird
calm and there's no talk about the new
冷静，没有关于新的说法
street address so is that the new
街道地址是新的
mailing address aren't actually our new
邮寄地址并不是我们的新东西
mailing address yeah he says street
邮寄地址是的，他说街道
address and I'm wondering if he's
地址，我想知道他是不是
wondering where we are physically right
想知道我们身体是否正确
now or where to send thing uh well new
现在或在哪里发送新的东西很好
street address it would be referring to
它会指的是街道地址
the mailing address we haven't
我们没有的邮寄地址
physically moved we've been here since
从那以后我们一直在这里身体感动
last year but there's a studio D but
去年但是有一家工作室 D但是
we've closed our postal box so now when
我们现在关闭了邮政信箱
you send us a postcard you're sending it
你寄给我们一张你寄来的明信片
to a physical address as opposed to a
到一个物理地址而不是一个
postal box so that's why that's
邮政信箱，所以这就是为什么
partially why things have changed so
部分为什么事情改变了
bald nerd calm is my blog and there's a
秃头的书呆子冷静是我的博客，有一个
blog there that talks all about why we
博客那里谈论所有关于我们为什么
made that change so check that out if
做了这个改变，所以检查一下 ，如果
you follow me on Twitter I've posted it
你在 Twitter上 关注我， 我发布了它
there but go to bald nerd calm at the
在那里，但去光头书呆子 冷静
current time and this is june second
目前的时间，这是六月二号
2015 it's the top blog because it's the
2015年，它是最热门的博客，因为它是
last one that i've posted but at the
最后一个 ，我已经发布，但在
same time you can you can do a quick
同时你可以快速做到
search on my site as well for pele box
搜索我的网站以及pele盒
or canada post down with canada post
或加拿大邮政下来与 加拿大邮政
know maybe that's not a search query
知道也许这不是一个搜索查询
down with canada post's alright so we
下来加拿大邮政的 好吧，所以我们
don't have a p.o box anywhere which
在任何地方都没有宝箱
saves bunch of well I caught ya about
节省了我抓到亚的一堆
one hundred and fifty dollars a year
一年一百五十美元
yeah saves us that so the new address
是的，节省了我们这么新的地址
does it cost
这是否成本？
money it is technically it like we're
它在技术上就像我们一样
paying for a box but it's a hundred
支付一盒，但它是一百
fifty dollars less per year than Canada
每年比加拿大减少五十美元
Post Canada Post us through the roof
邮政加拿大邮寄我们通过屋顶
expensive I know his shop around and
昂贵的我知道他的商店和
that's not I hate to say it but they
这不是我讨厌说的，但他们
unfortunately decided that they didn't
不幸的是他们决定他们没有
want our business but that's the way it
想要我们的业务，但就是这样
goes yeah so we're saving a boatload of
是啊，所以我们节省了一大笔钱
money by going somewhere else that gives
通过去别的地方赚钱
me better service and that's what my
我更好的服务，这就是我的
blog is about what is really really cool
博客是关于什么真的很酷
about where we are now when I get mail I
关于我现在在哪里，当我收到邮件我
get an email oh that's ideal how cool is
收到一封电子邮件哦，这是理想的酷
that I always thought why is Canada Post
我一直认为加拿大邮政是为什么
not doing that hmm because these days
因为这些日子没有这么做
there is no flag that you can put up
没有你可以忍受的旗帜
right so it's not like the old days
对，所以它不像过去那样
where we had a mailbox where you could
我们在哪里有一个邮箱，你可以
put up a flag and you see as you're
竖起旗帜，你看到你
pulling into the driveway I've got mail
拉进车道我有邮件
cuz the flag is up I'm surprised they
因为国旗已经升起，我很惊讶他们
haven't done that because I mean little
没有那样做，因为我的意思很小
things I I get an email when my Fitbit
当我的 Fitbit 时，事情II会收到一封电子邮件
battery runs low yeah and it emails it
电池电量低，是通过电子邮件发送的
emails me to say to charge it I get I
电子邮件我说给它充电，我得到我
know that you can text the transit
知道你可以给过境发短信
system here and find out when the buses
系统在这里， 并找出 什么时候巴士
is going to be at the next stop but our
将在下一站，但我们的
postal service that covers all of Canada
涵盖加拿大全境的邮政服务
right has no tech technology behind a
权利没有技术背后的技术
postbox that costs three hundred dollars
邮箱， 花费三百美元
a year that's crazy what are you guys
一年这是疯狂的你们是什么人
doing geez crazy so yeah I got an email
做geez疯狂所以是的，我收到 了一封电子邮件
is I before amazon told me that my item
是亚马逊之前告诉我的，我的物品
was delivered i got an email saying that
被送达了， 我收到一封电子邮件说
it was there that's how awesome is that
它在那里真是太棒了
so Michael can not find new every day
所以迈克尔每天都无法找到新的东西
anywhere but the rope Roku box so
任何地方，但绳Roku框如此
nowhere but Roku okay and also can't
无处不在，但Roku 没关系，也不能
find the show show boy oh boy I know
找到节目秀男孩哦，我知道的男孩
that okay let's let's back up real quick
那好吧，让我们让我们快速备份
Michael thank you so much for your email
迈克尔非常感谢你的电子邮件
and for those of you who have been
和那些你曾经的人
having any trouble finding things as we
像我们一样发现任何问题
grow we were category 5 technology TV
增长我们是第5类技术电视
for eight years mm-hmm then all of a
为八年毫米，然后所有的一个
sudden now we're category 5 TV network
突然现在 我们是第 5 类 电视网络
and we've got seven shows and the
我们有七个节目和
infrastructure is having to be
基础设施必须是
completely revamped and everything is
彻底改造，一切都是
being remodeled but category 5
正在改造，但类别5
technology TV has 400 episodes 400 pages
科技电视有400集400页
of content and everything has to be
的内容和一切都必须是
moved over to a new system so it's very
转移到一个新的系统，所以它非常
slow going but the new shows
慢，但新的节目
have their own new websites so when it
有他们自己的新网站，所以当它
comes to say new every day that is a
来说新的每一天，这是一个
program featuring you remember Carrie
节目特色你记得嘉莉
Webb who is co-host here season 1 season
韦伯在本赛季共同主持了赛季
2 ah yeah and if you go to new every day
2 嗯，如果你 每天都 去新的话
dot TV that's where you would go okay
点电视，这是你会好起来的地方
Michael so it's a web site on the web
迈克尔，所以它是一个网站上的网站
takes you there that's their website and
带你到那里他们的网站和
what it the reason that I suggested that
这是什么原因，我建议
last week is because if you point to
上周是因为如果你指向
category 5 TV you'll notice they're on
第5类电视，你会注意到 他们在
our new system for the network so they
我们新的网络系统，所以他们
have a list of all of our shows and
有我们 所有 的节目和列表
those shows if you click on them they
那些显示如果你点击他们他们
will take you those links will take you
将带你的那些链接将带你
to each of our programs and that reminds
到我们的每个程序，并提醒
me that I posted a new video on nature
我发布了一个关于大自然的新视频
sounds of Ontario Canada as well so make
加拿大安大略省的声音也如此
sure you check that out if you're into
当然，如果你愿意的话，你可以检查一下
solitudes relaxation and and just even
孤独放松， 甚至只是平静
listening to bird songs while you work
在工作时听鸟的歌
yes I'm just ambient noise in background
是的，我只是 背景中的 环境 噪音
um if we have helped you out tonight or
恩，如果我们帮助你今晚或者
at any time in the past please consider
在过去的任何时候请考虑
throwing a little tip into our tip jar
把一个小尖端扔进我们的尖罐里
at donate category 5 TV so if Robbie's
在捐赠第5类电视，所以如果罗比的
helped you figure out a problem or if
帮助你找出问题或者如果
I've helped you you know somehow have
不管怎样，我已经帮助过你
you enjoyed the show yeah made you laugh
你喜欢 这个节目让你笑了起来
thanks for support everybody yeah hope
感谢大家支持的希望
you enjoyed the show that's pretty close
你喜欢这个非常接近的节目
to all the time that we I know I we have
直到我们知道我们拥有的所有时间
another question but there's like not
另一个问题，但没有
enough time so let me just straight up
有足够的时间让我直起身来
say that spin gando we will get to you
说旋转gando我们会找到你
next week I promise you will be the
下周我保证你会成为你的
first question next week very good
下周第一个问题很好
another hour Reb D Jenk thank you so
另一个小时Reb D Jenk非常感谢你
much for being here everybody that's all
在这里，每个人都是这样
the time that we have don't forget make
我们不会忘记的时间
sure you get to our website category
确定你到达我们的网站类别
five dot TV you'll find our new
五点电视，你会发现我们的新
addressed a new address on the contact
在联系人上发了一个新地址
us or if you scroll down to the very
我们或者如果你向下滚动到这个位置
bottom of any of our pages on category
我们的任何页面的底部类别
five dot TV you'll see our new address
五点电视你会看到我们的新地址
send us a postcard the first five
给我们一张明信片的前五名
postcards to arrive at our new address
明信片到达我们的新地址
are going to automatically win a premium
将自动赢得溢价
vinyl category 5 logo sticker it's two
乙烯5类标志贴纸是两个
up so you get one dark one light so if
所以如果你得到一个黑暗的一个光
you've got a silver laptop you can put
你可以放一台银色笔记本电脑
the dark one on if you've got a black
黑色的，如果你有黑色的
laptop you can put the light one on
你可以把笔记本放在上面
you've got two stickers and they're both
你有两个贴纸，他们都是
they're both yours also anyone who sends
他们都是你的，也是任何发送的人
us postcard with in before july first is
我们的明信片在七月之前是第一次
going to be included in a draw to win a
将被包括在平局中以赢得一场比赛
full set of autographed category 5
全套亲笔签名类别5
business cards that's from category 5
来自第 5 类的名片
technology TV and some of them are rare
技术电视和其中一些是罕见的
finds as well because there are included
发现以及因为包括在内
in that business cards from people like
从那些人的名片喜欢
Abigail oh and Eric who hasn't been
阿比盖尔哦和埃里克谁没有
around for quite some time so those are
相当一段时间，所以这些都是
all included in that as well you find
所有包括在内，以及你找到
out more go to shop category 5 TV to see
多出去逛5类电视看看
the whole set and have you would love to
整套，并有你会喜欢
send that out to you don't forget to
发送给你不要忘记
make sure you stamp your postcard
确保你戳你的明信片
include your return mailing address so
包括你的回信邮寄地址
that we can send you your prize and send
我们可以向您发送奖品并发送
that to our new address and forget about
这对我们的新地址，而忘记 了
the old one forget you'll I'm sorry it
旧的忘记你我会很抱歉
ever happened okay have a fantastic week
曾经发生过好的一周
everybody see you next week thanks Sasha
大家下周都会见到你， 谢谢Sasha
thanks Adam Cathy bye bye mum happy
感谢Adam Cathy再见，妈妈高兴
birthday cheers buddy we hope you
生日欢呼伙计，我们希望你
enjoyed the show category 5 TV
欣赏5类电视节目
broadcasts live from Barrie Ontario
从Barrie Ontario直播
Canada every tuesday at seven p.m.
加拿大每星期二晚上七点
eastern if you're watching this on
东部如果你正在观看这个
demand or through cable TV check out the
需求或通过有线电视检查出来
local show times in your area at
在你所在地区的当地演出时间
category-five TV and find out when you
五类电视，并找出你的时间
can watch live and interact in the
可以观看现场直播和互动
community chat room category 5 is a
社区聊天室类别5是一个
production of prodigy digital solutions
生产神童数字解决方案
and is licensed under creative commons
并获得创意共享
attribution 2.5 canada we'll see you
归属地2.5加拿大我们会见到你
next time thanks for tuning in
下次感谢 调整